Okay, that's it, together.
This is now my heroes on the stock exchange.
I'm going to explain the thing with the bees and the
birds.
After that, we'll do the last
class
[Music]. A
good one is that she should have all four
legs. You should know how to
present things to people. Tree
number three: conscious behavior and
professional behavior. Number four:
We have one this time. How to
organize an event. Final:
How to show taxes. The topic of depression
is professional behavior,
and I think I'd like to talk
about voting rights today. And it happens in
a word. Advice that I gave, we didn't even have
the hormones, and there are
also pictures that go with them.
But we'll be it now.
We'll just give the presentation through the
title. As a teacher, a big day,
professional, though, how do you behave?
How do men behave towards
women and women towards men? And in the
monastery, it's really amazing to
get the hand, and maybe more
men come to Western countries.
I think I brought them here. I made
them learn, and education was
organized, and six of them took their
vows, and I stopped doing that. That's how
important it is.
to talk about it if such a teacher is
supposed to be open and honest at the
same time not be too shy,
I told you, I told you so much,
I have to do it quickly, wait a minute,
quickly, I have to send something to him,
individual, I can't believe it, now
I've sent it,
almost sent it, the market is there and in
America, parents tell their children the special thing, it says
if they do, because there are very
specific ones and even the children
know nothing about sex and when the child
saw 13, 14
and then the parents should
actually explain to them how to use contraception and
so on and AIDS, HIV,
I think the first picture please, okay,
what is interesting is flowers and resource
of sex, flowers and trees also have their
own history, the worst and in the
history of the West, the trees
studied how to reproduce, Christian
Marx, a Christian monk in
Europe, in the trash, in the Middle Ages,
the master of the house had babies,
who discovered the way into the heritage, trees
and flowers, reproducing media
streams, decision not to use, and they
then told me and they then told me
Latin  Words used for this are
triesman and trees plants and all
sexual organs of a flower hamm
Latin names because they wanted them to be ashamed
they didn't want
people to understand
flowers that vagina sperm everything is
normal that there is the word as well as a
foreseeable Marius Pohl him but I
think they were ashamed
who before has the light has the orange
color and the female which he believes
that the colors is weathered and why
she signs herself in the color it's
about reproduction because the young
sexy for that just as much and after the 5
bari is after in the fall line all would be
all infected plants trees produce more
they don't want their line to die out
continue to reproduce and
that is the main purpose of a plant that is what it does all the
time is
noticed further and as
especially with many years they in the
west decided to use Latin words
I don't know how that is China
a living being is as strong as a
bomb every life things trees plants
animals  Fish for humans, the
main purpose of the body is to
produce the same thing.
It's a very deep one with the motto "in
place," that's everyone, which means that this makes
love blind. Don Quixote, that
's like Don Quixote.
I think I already mentioned the first
page. There were 1000 pages long.
How did it come about that love makes you blind? Because of hormones.
We will do everything to be with another person. Humans,
plants, and animals do
it the same way. It's a very strong
drive. We all believe that we don't care
about someone. About this type, all
teachers have it, and all students have it
completely in people, and it also makes
the landlords.
I'm the guy who crashed the ship into the
rocks,
so I can explain to you how it
works because I crashed my ship
into the rocks. Danger. If the energy
and the greatest feeling in people,
you have atomic bombs between your
legs, nominate that. Nobody made us do that.
My parents didn't tell me.
I discovered it for myself.
So, from the skin to the path of life, there is more
life to give.
That's a good one.  Without these years of
strength, we wouldn't be here. Our
parents wouldn't have made us otherwise.
In the next one, the pistol is there. What's it called in
German? It appeared, has the
eggs and they come, and the pollen is the
hair of Flex, or a flower can have
sex with itself. More port switches, the
male part can make the pollen
and give the stigma over the
female part, and then a
new flower will emerge. Imbert Domingo,
that's the goal of a sum, to get the
seed into the female part,
and with humans, it's so much more.
Ready, do
n't look so ashamed, I do it too.
I'll tell you now what he actually is.
Your parents should have brought two,
and that's why the flowers have such
wonderful colors, beauty, but only
to produce them. Yes, of course,
a flower can self-pollinate,
but that would be the same as if a man
married his sister, and the
bloodline, the genes, will always get
weaker.
It's much better if that's the
sperm, the pollen, but a
successful one to a vagina of another
believer.
Now you know why.  The flowers are so pretty so that
the bees are attracted,
but also the bees
have such a small flag that they
only want the way there is this
great thing similar to how perfectly the
ladies' names appeared,
the bee world only the juice would be randomly,
then it would be sperm on the hairs
on its little ones sticking. I don't know
who made the plan, so they
actually only wanted the flowers, and
when they fly away from the flower, it is
their legs that are borrowed from
someone else or called, and
then they fly to the sixth flower, and
the other one falls on the other
flower, and that's why the flowers are so
beautiful, or didn't they design the flowers for the
district so
that they could reproduce. The
flower tries to look at the bee so that
it brings the seed to the next plant,
and that's how
the flowers cross.
I have flowers in my garden, a
beer tree now,
it is a very tree, the side space in
Essen, and there are male and
female trees.
I think in Munich, in Phoenix,
you are not allowed to have female trees.  Mulberry trees are
planted, they pollute
the environment with their fruit. From
June onwards, the
flower is there,
that's just some things that have changed.
I really didn't want to
use the words, they didn't want to
use direct language, but then
the plans are made, she gets pregnant, it's too early,
and then it will also be outside, the
leaves fall off, we are
pregnant now, we don't need the leaves
anymore, if the women stop
wearing miniskirts because they are already
pregnant, because it
worked,
she is pregnant and needs, and then
the watermelon grows in the fruit,
that's 1000 new things in the end, in a
pregnant woman, not twins, triplets,
there are 1000 babies inside, and each of them
has the power to make another 1000, it
is very, very powerful.
The rose also gets a fruit, and
that when the next generation of
roses is
very interesting, if you want that
inclusion must finally happen, when as soon as
they have it on the arm, you cut
the huge part, in April, there are whole
men every day, as the EU calls, stuck,
when you see the rose  God cuts it off, that
's like abortion. The feeling is, I have to
produce a new flower to
attract new finances.
This desire, which I want to
reproduce, is the strongest.
Plant it in LinkedIn, and the fruits of
the watermelon, that's
too big for me.
The purpose of it, why are we talking about it?
The six stayed in the Mevza. Tears.
I'll come back to that.
Merkel, the next picture should be of a
beautiful woman. Jersey, that's her.
Ladies, women do the same
flowers.
This is in this picture. Both are
depicted.
If you're with the coach, women get high.
What was brought in about the office of
must be more beautiful. Truck clos. You must have
seen beautiful clothes. One before 4000
and that's currently for around 6000 years
and everyone has one on top. You did
n't think about it, but
your wife, your country, you have your
history up close. A culture brings
the two mega makeup of the clutch
herring Adobe. Why? Because we need
a vein.
That concerned choosing, and we've been doing that
for thousands of years.
It's not beautiful, it's we need
egg bottles,
I love it but it's also dangerous, so
be the real reason for small
makeup, even for boys, because the letters with
the bright colors are the men
and their coaches,
and that's not even what's aimed at,
it's not why he
's on TV, lipstick advertising, I'd be a De
La Concorde high chair, we cut it short
and the whole story in a
cultural center is brainwashing,
if no women are made up and do
n't wear good clothes then
they are not great,
Veronika was introduced to us, had
three sisters and her mother did
n't want her to leave the house
and when we visit her, she shows
her 94, the factions and the meaning and
purpose of the whole thing is not just
exactly like being daily for beauty or
chronic, but to have bees,
why do we need more people?
If everyone stops
reproducing
then the human race will die
out, it is a very powerful
human way to make a baby, there is
a difference between
women and men,
the blues, most  Women
menstruate for the first time at 15, or
whenever, at the moment
menstruation begins, the green blooms,
but the desire for
a man persists, and every 35-year-old man only then do
the reproductive years
end again.
Before, she wanted to take a hill at 35.
Every woman should have a baby before 40.
This desire is something Otto and
more people have.
Marrying at 30 is something for someone who does
n't want to get married. They should go back to being
single, gladly divorced again.
She doesn't understand what's going on; they
simply want more.
They don't understand what's happening. Once, but
unfortunately,
I looked it up. This is new: the
sex party. Fischer is blocking. Men have
the same desire, and new ones from 16 to 69.
The sperm are active
because women's desire eventually diminishes, but
for men, it remains. It's a desire that persists for a
very long time, even in pornography
on the internet.
If you also have it, that's good, but it
's similar. Will it stop? I
need a girl. It's very strong when
a man speaks warmly at the BBC about
finances, generating genes, and the
probability of having a sick baby.
Having is higher because there is 25, so
the horny one is a phase in men
between 25 and 16,
and it's not the mafia that keeps
the sex business going, it's
not the pornography left, they are
men who want that.
I think it was Engels, 3 percent of all
men in the world, and Halo
cinema for Wissmann could watch
pornography at least once a month,
and that's a large proportion of all
men worldwide who watch pornography
once or twice a month.
I'll tell you the address later, it will be
useful.
Why are we talking about all this? You're going to
be reactive. You have your rope, he that it will be,
and when you get up and under just the...
they are there, there are many bees
and flowers in the audience, cheering
when you put a first picture, an available
demo, Romero Sabine on stage,
all women, all men rob.
If you still put the women over green,
half of the men were
visibly in love, no matter if you're on
stage, Alto... before they fall in love...
stage and not into
the person,
I already announced it was a
great woman,
her book, I tried not to be so good
and then I wanted to say hello
and then she was already gone again, be
aware that they don't see
you, they fall in love, but they fall in love with
the stage, if someone else is
standing there, he would have taught the same class,
then the same
girl would be for that guy, they
just need to be next to him and 7,
there is this desire for a vein,
they understand each other but they don't, they act, desire
but they don't know how to, the truly
handsome boys, and I
wonder if your girlfriend, so the purpose
of today's lecture, get used to it,
and there it was, it's a fund, it's a
very powerful man, her sideways,
especially, they just have hormones, I
wasn't into it,
Mosley, I Ovechkin came and told
me, many people have made these
mistakes and many have failed,
and we knew them out, and
that's not just young people but also
women, so many women wanted to be involved
with all men,
so if she goes on stage and seven
and users are standing  On stage and
someone falls in love with you. With
rock musicians, they
threw their underwear on stage. Is
that easy?
Bees are hormones.
It's not very romantic. Of course,
some fall in love. That's okay too. There's
a difference between
adult love, love for the
right reasons, and just all or nothing. At the
end of my presentation, I have to
explain the difference to you.
Here are a few problems
we should think about:
how do you get number 1 because of your
hormones? If two people
ask a question, and you are one version
of a young man and the other is a
pretty young woman, the other is an
old woman, you will answer the
pretty young woman's question first by
order. This is unconscious, the hormone
controlled the behavior. Therefore, you have to be
careful. A teacher must treat all students
equally, whether the hormones are old or
young, or an available one, and has
the flower. Treat everyone
equally. If you ask
the young girl first during question and answer, it's a
hormone problem, and that's why it's good if
another teacher is there. It's good
in  Teaching couples because then you can
learn and then your friend will
tell the truth to your face. Educate yourself if
you are aware that she answers with
the car of the pretty young girls,
so it's good if you
are taught by someone else, preferably
someone of the opposite sex.
I ask him to let you know
if people are
treated the same, that you can control the hormones there.
[Music]
How do I behave as every other
country has different rules, warned who
can touch.
In America, it's like that, the vice president
and the hair of women. When I
was in Mexico, I touched a woman on one
cheek until French offered. We are
Mexicans, we know about both
cheeks. Sorry,
I didn't mean to annoy you. Motto:
We don't do that. And
then ask someone where I need another
private lesson. Ca
n't I have the email address or
maybe how? You have to ask even
deeper questions.
If you think you are...
If you believe this is a pure question,
then you can give your email address more.
But if you believe that it is not...
But one is then answer them
if I already if I've already
taught then I think something
is already an expert or factions
I give you a strategy a
suggestion I never have anyone
I ask for the email and if you
think they just want to be there
I'm not really good at that but my
dreams and if they never contacted the friend
then they had a hormone to tackle
what do I do if I'm on a
bed and 7 really like like Scott
Ohrid and Peter and are we allowed to make
dates can we have a
good season yes but talk to
his partner teacher this time
this person let me dress I have
no case do the reality check
with a course if you have to check out twelve women
in a year then it's
probably his hormones that
speak harmoniously with us and we ca
n't change our behavior and
I'm just being honest with you
and before that we had many problems with it
and also with that
I would like to execute the women's titles
then you should follow the bachelor's
advice first since their
engine meet because  It will be like this later,
no question, always you are you, not time,
they won't
look like a flower for 50 years.
Be honest with yourself, I meet
with my mother,
and if you still believe
I've met my partner,
then I meet with her, but be
honest with yourself. Many, many
married couples have failed because the
man lost his hair or the woman
had wrinkles on her face, and then you look at
the selection, Gini, and then
they get involved because it's wonderful to be enough
with yourself. A marriage is
his, it makes a
lifelong promise, so if you
try, you experience your partner on a
donkey, find new events, be
honest with yourself, love and honor,
Google through illness and death, for that, death separates us, even Lord,
you will be ugly when
you are old, even if you had to drive the other
wheelchair to Rome, I want to be
married to him.
[Music]
is, yes, if it is, heard from students,
we will have a secret channel to ECE
management, and every student can
secretly talk about you, how hard in
English  The incident in the middle block: 45
women find out that the teacher is
doing bad things, but you can't
tell anyone. We'll have
an email about it, the exercise isn't with
your name.
I think the teacher has six
girlfriends; he has a hormone problem.
Sometimes the students will also
write that they don't like you, not
because you do something. Yes, we're there, but we won't pretend,
and we'll also check out the
student. We won't get the winnings just
because someone receives a letter.
After the first letter, we'll check,
but we'll see that it's very important.
So, as a teacher, TTC Hasberg has to
respect other people's relationships, especially
married people in committed relationships. Be super, super
careful. What's the
general rule?
Always imagine that the woman
or man is there. Would you flirt with them?
Would you flirt if the
other person's partner is there? That's a good
rule: respect physical boundaries.
Every country has different rules. In some
countries, you can hug people,
like in Mexico. That's natural. If you
meet someone, then hug them.
I think  In Asia, it does
n't really affect me.
The border is because every country has its
own rules. Teachers
teach in many countries,
so you should know the rules of the
country where the class is held. Is it
a hug or a handshake?
After five years, shaking hands is perfectly normal. It's
very safe, and if someone does it, it's
good.
People like that. It's very
American. In the next picture of the
circle,
a Western man is
shaking hands with an Asian woman. Maybe
he's crossing a line. You have to
learn the rules. The students shouldn't...
You have to be friendly towards our students, but find out
what the rules are in this country.
Where is the limit?
How should that be? It should be loving, for example, like to put
the frame around people.
If you pat someone on the shoulder,
Esterhazy did a good job, but make
sure that's in the country, otherwise
hurting people is like Lego, illegal
problems, legal problems.
I have friends. 30 years ago, they
founded a yoga center. It was the
biggest in America. They worked hard for 30 years
because Warner Petit, one of the teachers,
had sex with a student. So, it was
a woman with a woman, and the
woman ransacked the yoga studio. I
know, it's a bit like China, but
in America, you can file a lawsuit, and
she won, and as a result,
the yoga studio had to close. They had to
sell the yoga studio. 30 years of hard
work destroyed in a dream by one of the
teachers. That couldn't be with Tim. He
had his heart attack because then he has to
find a new job and experience this
job, and we live. So, if you
risk something like that, you also have legal problems, sure.
Kosovo and it's hardly possible that he
might even be sued,
the pollen and Libya can't
control it, I can destroy it even
if the police don't catch it, the
internet will get you and if you're
attracted to someone, then I tried
to remind you that you've been
working on this for 25 years, so many people so hard, so
many translating, hard work, a bee
with lots of harmony and destruction on the
internet, it's so easy that you
chatted on the internet